now what about how do you maintain the
level if because God aren't you having
it is there a continuous flow of water
through here or do sit a batch process
if you when you hook it up to the the
reservoir over here you can actually see
the level that you're at okay when I've
got it like this I just know that I'm
going to run it for you no I'm just
gonna pour in a gallon and a half and
let it go but if you have a reservoir
over here you can actually raise the
raise and lower the reservoir and you'll
see the line of the water and you just
adjust as just as you see fit
you really want the water to be right
about the top of the plates maybe just a
little bit lower and that's fine so with
the reservoir it makes it very easy so
give us a step process number one you
put the water number two you put the lid
on this okay number one you take your
water whenever you water you're going to
use whether it's going to be spring
water if you're going to be brave and
try a salt salt lake water or ocean
water your water or or my water my
elements mix that all up together in a
system like this you're looking at about
a yell and a half we've been yelling in
the quarter like I said you put this in
a five-gallon bucket and that's really
easy okay my plates are sitting about
six inches off the bottom I know that
I'm gonna put into a nap gallons okay
but measure us your water find out
exactly how much you want pour that in
there and then actually you want to seal
this first because you can add your
water here so you want to seal this up
because this is not going to seal
properly if it gets wet and when you're
walking around and trying to get all
these bolts that's why actually they're
all unequal so that it's easier to put
them on and then just come down how much
time do you have to work with with that
plumbers uh how long does it setup you
want you want us be sealing it up
thin about within less than 10 minutes
okay I like I like to give it about five
minutes on a cool day I'll I won't worry
about it too much but on a hot day I
wanted to seal it up within five minutes
okay and that includes putting the nuts
on yep well you you you put it in place
and then you just start tightening down
the nuts depending on on your mechanism
of sealing I actually told you with the
idea of putting a clamp on there
clamping it down and then tightening
down the nuts and that works too but you
know you you put it in place and that's
the first stage and then you tighten
down your nuts and you want all that
done within within ten minutes okay
and then let's talk about filling up the
reservoir since we don't have the
reservoir to demonstrate here can you
can we use something just as a visual
okay so we're here and this hose go to
the bottom and this is we go to the top
let's permit for the actually the
earlier portion where we're describing
the components let's describe the
reservoir okay actually this is this is
the this is the present right here so as
you can see the reservoir is actually
higher than the highest level of this
hydrogen device and there's different
ways to play with this and I don't want
to go into the - hey of that because it
really comes down to personal preference
but as you can see filling up this
device will bring you to right about
here okay and so what and so you can
actually see how much water you have in
your hydrogen device by the level in
your reservoir okay and so you open that
up pour it in fill it up to there it
equalizes it drops down you fill it up
again and you're you're fine my
preferences on size of reservoir know
it's it's totally personal preference
these things are eight bucks apiece so
I've said hey can argue with that I'm
just gonna buy them and put them in
place it's eight dollars so they're
fairly pretty cheap and not not
difficult to use and using the same
reservoir on this system over here yep
same deal okay because I had a lot of
laying around okay this is a safety
bubbler you're not going to be running
an engine off of this thing well maybe
you are if you're running an engine off
of this thing you want to run it through
a safety bubbler right so let's just
stick with this scenario doing that
let's now pretend like this is your
reservoir okay for demonstration
purposes so we're going to run this
bottom hose to the bottom of this
reservoir run the top hose to the top of
this reservoir and we're going to look
and see where the level of our plates
are compared to where course wants to on
this on this reservoir okay and so we're
going to fill up the reservoir to the
level that we that is indicated by where
the plates are so you're pouring the
water into the reservoir yes you're
pouring the water into the reservoir and
you poured water down into the reservoir
and it will this will equalize pretty
quickly so basically as fast as you can
pour it in it's going to flow in there
and equalize and when you reach the
proper level that's where you stop you
can play around with it the time I want
to put a bar on the outside of this just
to be sure right exactly and then also
you're gonna want to have some way to
fasten your reservoir in relation to the
maintain so that they're not moving back
and forth and right like on my in my
video presentation I had a picture of my
entire safety set up on the wall and
part of that was the reservoir yeah and
I feed this unit with that same
reservoir that I feed all my other
hydrogen myths so they're all daisy
chained together so that's it's pretty
simple okay so that's that's the setup
and I'm assuming that people are just
going to let this let this hydrogen boil
off into the air if you're inside you
want to run the hose to the outside if
you are letting this sit outside you're
fine you can you can bubble it off
through a through a safety bubbler or
something run into a generator whatever
your whatever your preference is what if
you are in the alchemical process you're
experimenting and you've got some kind
of a toxic substance that you're
replicating then you would probably are
you going to have any of that coming out
what you want is a if you're playing
with that stuff it's gonna be pretty
advanced but if you're playing with that
stuff you want to have multiple washes
of water now the other the other this
this container right here is the safety
bubbler and the wash okay
and what happens is the gas bubbles
through there and any particulate to any
any residual from the machine is going
to collect in that in the second bubbler
and what you want if you're playing with
toxic stuff you want multiple stages of
those so by the time you get down here
your gas is completely cleaning you want
them to be tall to I use I use a
harvelle clear PVC pipes but caps on the
end and bubble gaps through it because I
can actually see I'm a very visual
person I can actually see the bubbles
and I can see the gas escaping I saw a
$50,000 hydrogen prototype destroyed in
ten minutes because he had no visual
feedback okay he relied entirely upon
computer gizmos and gadgets to tell him
what was going on and one of them failed
it was like a China Syndrome a 25 cent
piece failed and a fifty thousand dollar
prototype was destroyed after 10 minutes
very big fan of visual feedback one
bubbler would have told him that
something was wrong but he thought but
he was relying on a computer so the
visual feedback on top of that and as I
mentioned in my lecture if you got a
long column of water and you're bubbling
hydrogen through it have fun with it put
a rodent coil around it see what happens
we're dealing with a with a practically
an electrolytic gas here yes
try energizing it with with high
frequency energies and such there's one
guy that was playing with us back in the
60s and he would have a little separator
is the most inefficient thing on the
face of the planet but then he'd run it
between two eight inch plates very
similar to my lids there
he ran between two eight inch plates
that were separated about two inches
apart that would had a high-voltage
Corona in the center of it not
- not enough spark to ignite it but
enough but enough energy to turn that
hydrogen gas into deuterium and he was
running this car on so play with columns
shine lasers through it sine ultraviolet
lasers through it do different stuff
like that and you'll start to see the
quality of gas change and start to see
the manifestation I
I swear someday we're going to see
somebody running a torch and they're
gonna start depositing gold on a piece
of steel and that'll be really cool so
anyway that's the setup if you're
working with the experiment working with
elements like that you want to have
multiple stages just to make certain
that whatever you escaped off into the
air or what have you bleed off into the
air is going to be it's gonna be clean
what about the edge you're running this
are you expecting the water level to
drop edit it's not gonna drop super fast
since we're only producing like I said
this one's going 20 liters an hour
there's your expansion ratio is at least
1,800 to 1
so 1800 liters is going to take a little
while to go through and that's burning
through one gallon of water but if
you're bleeding it off and taking your
minerals out that your video that you're
multiplying then you just you know keep
on adding water in proportion to the
minerals or the water that you've taken
out let's talk about harvesting minerals
and you've got the set up where you've
got the the reservoir and where where
the minerals showing up and that even
the minerals are showing up in the water
that comes out of here and collects in
your reservoir and what you're going to
do there's a number of different ways to
work with that
I would suggest everybody gets the book
recovery and processes precious metals
by Bill Eamon because that is the
definitive work tuning on how to recover
elements from any city any situation
whether it be an ore or a ore deposit or
whatever your
working with him solenoidal what was
that - line ride from an oil well oh
really
you missed it yesterday I talked about
my oil well extra hints there
oh I didn't I didn't get back in time I
didn't get down time to hear about it
but we processed water from three oil
wells stripper wells the brine was
considered so strong but it was
hazardous waste and it had to be diluted
before it could be rejected
really and the wells produced maybe two
barrels a week in 98 Brian did you ever
do that analyst analysis on the on the
brine I got to I was able to smelt out
of the we get your process okay and the
waste the precipitate we had worked with
and I got 8 ounces of silver wow that's
good stuff I love it excellent sounds
like a blast
yeah but the same thing it's a you have
to find a place to have a fun place to
the process of Pancakes did you yeah
this process to precipitate out and drop
out oh yeah we we ran up we were pulling
20 amps we've had an outdoor tank did
you dare to stuff in on the plates
because cone-shaped tank so we collect a
to collect precipitated out afterwards
and we would run at ice until the
voltage went to zip because assaults
were all collected the recipient very
afterwards in the process of the Pacific
time after that
and well in this particular v it was
very little cold and there was some
platinum but very little going going
back to none another affirmation of
what's going on here
yeah well that's that's the rot right
now and there's nothing multiplying but
that's the dropping out so there we go
exactly we're actually part a part of
this element we missed the first part is
actually about multiplication of
elements - yes
which is which they're the hydrogen
oxygen and the energy assist happening
quite abundant like I'd like to talk to
you say here's another smart man and
working with silver not that stupid
could you could you that's excellent now
thank you
hey you don't mind us including that in
our YouTube video here I see no reason
okay alright so pour my water my
elements mix that all up together in a
system like this you're looking at about
a yelling half they've been yelling a
quarter like I said you can put this in
a five-gallon bucket and that's really
easy okay my plates are sitting about
six inches off the bottom
I know that I'm gonna put into an
afghans okay but measure us your water
find out exactly how much you want pour
that in there and then actually you want
to seal this first because you can add
your water here so you want to seal this
up because this is not going to seal
properly if it gets wet and when you're
walking around and trying to get all
these bolts that's why actually they're
all unequal so that
it's easier to put them on like okay
this is one and then that point that one
and then you just suck them down how
much time you have to work with with
that plumbers uh how long does it set up
you want you want us be sealing it up
with it about within less than ten
minutes okay I like I like to give it
about five minutes on a cool day I'll I
won't worry about it too much but on a
hot day I want to seal it up within five
minutes okay and that includes putting
the nuts on yep well you you you put it
in place and then you just start
tightening down the nuts depending on on
your mechanism of sealing I actually
told them if the idea of putting a clamp
on there climbing it down and then
tightening down the nuts and that works
too but you know you you put it in place
and that's the first stage and then you
tighten down your nuts and you want all
that done with him within ten minutes
okay and then let's talk and you just
adjust as just as you see it you really
want the water to be right about the top
of the plates maybe just a little bit
lower and that's fine so with the
reservoir it makes it very easy so give
us a step process number one you put the
water number two you put the lid on is
okay number one you take your water
whatever you want are you going to use
whether it's going to be spring water if
you're going to be brave and try a salt
salt lake water or ocean water your
water or now what about how do you
maintain the level if because aren't you
having it is there a continuous flow of
water through here or you do set a batch
process if you when you hook it up to
the the reservoir over here you can
actually see the level that you're at
okay when I've done it like this I just
know that I'm going to run it for you
know I'm just gonna pour in a gallon and
a half
let it go but if you have a reservoir
over here you can actually raise the
raise and lower the reservoir and you'll
see the line of the water